<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Emilio&#39;s Murmurs</title>
    <link>https://em1l1o.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Emilio&#39;s Murmurs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 10:29:10 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://em1l1o.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a RSpec CI Pipeline Using Jenkins and Docker</title>
      <link>https://em1l1o.github.io/posts/build_a_ci_pipeline_with_jenkins_and_docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 10:29:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://em1l1o.github.io/posts/build_a_ci_pipeline_with_jenkins_and_docker/</guid>
      <description>Background Due to the lack of CI, I have to run RSpec manually every time I am about to merge my feature branch into master branch. It&amp;rsquo;s an exhausting and forgettable yet important chore. People are unreliable, however, it is just a matter of time before something goes wrong. That&amp;rsquo;s why I decided to build our CI pipeline to run RSpec.
CI Options I have CircleCI and Jenkins under consideration. However, we have to pay to use CircleCI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Track Down a Ruby Memory Leak Issue</title>
      <link>https://em1l1o.github.io/posts/trace_down_a_memory_leak_issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:09:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://em1l1o.github.io/posts/trace_down_a_memory_leak_issue/</guid>
      <description>Background I found that our production instances memory utilization exceeded the threshold frequently in the past few weeks. This was what it looked like:
In the past one month (even longer), there&amp;rsquo;s an incremental memory consumption in our application. And one day, it exceeded the line.
Actually, the same had been happening to our test instance for a long time, due to many cron jobs that won&amp;rsquo;t exit as expected. As time goes by, more and more memory was consumed by them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deal With the Failure of IAM Role Detachment</title>
      <link>https://em1l1o.github.io/posts/fix_iam_role_detachment_issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 22:46:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://em1l1o.github.io/posts/fix_iam_role_detachment_issue/</guid>
      <description>Background One day I found that we&amp;rsquo;ve lost days of monitoring data of some instances, so I logged into one of these instances and run the CloudWatch monitoring script manually to send some data to AWS. However, I got this message from AWS:
The security token included in the request is expired
 Security credentials are required in order to use services and resources of AWS, and it is very convenient to manage these credentials via IAM roles, which is the way we&amp;rsquo;ve always done it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>